digeus.com 2008-06-03

# Digeus Inc. | Privacy Policy

The following is the privacy policy for the www.Digeus.com Web site. In this policy, we describe what personal information we collect on our site, how we use it, and your options regarding information we may collect about you. If you have questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at:

**Digeus Corporation**   
2405 Woodlake Dr.   
Okemos, MI 48864-5910 USA

**Tollfree:** 800.517.3001 (U.S. Only)   
**Voice:** +1.517.381.2300   
**Fax:** +1.517.913.6121

**Our Privacy Policy**

Digeus Corporation collects cookies on our Web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and we use this information only internally- we never give away information about our users- to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. If you choose to e-mail us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, we will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. We will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties. If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact our webmaster.

**Volunteered Information**

When you purchase something on our site, we collect personal information from you including your shipping address, credit card number and the e-mail address to use for order confirmation. This information is collected on Web pages using encryption technology to help prevent any third party from intercepting the information. Your credit card information is only used for completing the purchase transaction and is retained only as necessary for administration purposes. We use the information provided by our customers to analyze product trends based on, for example, geographic and demographic factors. This analysis helps us improve the quality of our Web site and product mix.

**Information Collected in Contests**

If you enter one of our contests, the data we collect will be handled according to the rules of that particular contest and those rules may differ based on where you live. We provide a privacy policy specific to each contest that you should review prior to entering the contest.

Accessing Your Information

Customers may access their contact information through e-mail or customer service center in order to correct discrepancies and update records with new address information. See contact information at the beginning of this policy.

Forums

Membership into our forums is voluntary. When you provide your username, password and e-mail address, you can receive online support from Digeus and from other Digeus software users. Please refer to the policy before registering to join our forums.

Newsletters

Subscription to a Digeus newsletter is voluntary. By providing your e-mail address, you are agreeing that Digeus can send you important information about our products, including announcements of new releases. You may update your e-mail address or unsubscribe via Web form at any time at http://www.Digeus.com/community/subscription.asp.

Downloading Software

When you download a Digeus product, Digeus asks you to provide your e-mail address in order to guide you through the 30-day trial period of using the software. We do not verify the validity of the e-mail address. You may unsubscribe from the follow up e-mails by contacting our webmaster at any time.

Updates to this Policy

As our Web site evolves over time or our data handling policies change, we will update this privacy policy. Changes made to this policy will be effective ten days following the posting of the new policy on the Web site. If we make significant changes to our data handling practices, we will make efforts to notify our active customers in other reasonable ways that may include an administrative email or other notice. This privacy policy will be governed by the laws of the United States and the State of Michigan.

Security

Digeus is committed to security and protecting your privacy. Digeus promises to quickly work to remedy any vulnerabilities found in our website or software and to alert our customers about any potentially dangerous vulnerabilities. If you have questions about Digeus's committment to security or concerns about a security issue in one of our products or website, please visit our security center.

Last Updated: 05/25/2008 18:40:06
